Thank you for watching!
Now, that said, we are here at the Hakata Lake Observation Deck.
There's a great fresh breeze blowing.
So, what are the six of us doing here today?
Miyu, have you grown taller?
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm surprised.
I hate it when you get a little taller just because you graduated.
You'll grow taller if you do this.
Yes, that's right.
It's like that.
You scared me. Now you're doing it.
I'm surprised to see you here.
I don't know what the six of us are going to do.
Well, we've got someone here who can tell us.
Please come on in!
Good morning.
I'm Hamada, the chairperson of the Boo-Boo executive committee.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Oh! Oh!
LOL!
Laughing.
What's this?
Bon appétit.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Laughing.
Yum!
Delicious!
It's so good!
Today is the second
day of exchange between Japanese and Korean students!
Yes, sir.
Last time, we had a curry party with the students.
We made curry with the students.
We made curry and rice.
We made curry and rice, right?
Chocolate... like this big one! I did it.
I also have a scene of "One Pan Man Chocolate Dawn! We have a scene from the "One-Pan Man Chocolate Dawn!
This time, we will be able to meet again.
This time, we will go across the sea to Busan!
I'm going to Pusan!
Oh!
But if you're in Pusan and you're at the Port of Hakata right now, that means you're coming to the Port of Hakata
This time
I'm going on that ferry.
Oh!
You're going on the Queen Beat?
Oh, that's fun!
It's fun.
What's that? Suddenly...
He didn't jump or anything.
Hello.
Is this what you were translating the last time we made curry?
Hello. My name is Hwang. I work for JR Kyushu Express Line.
Nice to meet you.
Mr. Fan.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Fan.
You mean you're from JR Kyushu High Speed Rail?
That's right.
No, I'm not.
So you're going on the Queen Beetle this time?
Yes, that's right.
It takes 3 hours and 40 minutes to get to Musan, Korea.
We'll take you all on the Queen Beetle to Musan now.
We'll be there for two days and one night.
We'd like you all to get excited before the battening down of the hatches.
You know, this is important, because I hear we're taking a lot of heat.
A lot is at stake.
It's going to cost a lot.
Well, that's why the three of us have been doing this for a while now.
We did our best last time.
Today, the three of us...
Teach me some things.
Okay, everyone, let's head to the mountains.
Hey!
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
And up here...
Curry's big winner!
The big winner?
We won, didn't we?
I'm going to eat.
I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it.
I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it.
It's not good.
Winner is No. 3
No, it's not.No, it's not.
No, it wasn't.
Was the food good?
We did our best.
We're a competitive team with a lot of time to spare.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!
Everything will be perfect without the chocolate!
Good night!
We're aboard!
Yay!
Have you three been on board before?
It's your first time, isn't it?
First time.
Have you ever been to Korea?
It's our first time.
First time?
So, I'd like to start exploring the ship now.
I'd like to explore the ship.
Mr. Huang, may I ask you to show me around?
I'll show you around.
Yes, please.
This is the ship's duty free store. Duty free as long as you don't leave the country.
Dutifully, right? We can't buy duty-free items that are exempt from taxes.
But since we're on our way to Korea, we can use this duty-free store.
Sensei's souvenirs are all over the place!
It's true!
Mentaiko! Mentaiko!
Japanese souvenirs, Korean souvenirs, that Korean seaweed.
That sweet coffee from Korea. This is delicious... instant coffee.
And Lila's favorite, strawberries. Lots of strawberries. Sweet too.
And those perfumes.
Especially the most popular one.
The face wash.
You're right. People stop by Donki a lot.
This is number one. Just like it says.
The feature of this boat is that it's packed with bicycles.
That's great.
When people from Korea come to Japan for cycling
I'm going to bring it over here.
They can get on the boat and
and ride around in Japan as much as they want.
Most of them go to Oita, Kumamoto, and Kagoshima.
Kagoshima?
I know some people who go to Kagoshima.
Do you usually ride bicycles in Korea?
Yes, yes, yes.
There are a lot of bicycle riding groups in Korea.
The equipment is quite luxurious, isn't it?
Yes, please look this way.
Yes, sir.
This is the museum on board.
Art museum
The entire ship was designed by Ms. Mitoka Mito, an industrial designer who designed the ship based on this concept.
The entire ship was designed by Ms. Kaori Mitoka, an industrial designer, and is now decorated with various items designed by her.
Wow, that's great!
It's a very relaxing, museum-like space.
Which painting is your favorite?
There are so many.
I like the second one from the right of the colorful paintings.
Which one is it?
The middle one.
It's really cute, and it pops.
The second one from the right is kind of...
It's kind of cool.
You're right.
They all look like department store paper bags.
It certainly looks like it could be.
Hey, fashionable resume make-up!
Next to this, we're going to be on the observation deck that goes outside on the third floor, so...
Yay!
We're going to go up a little bit from the back.
It's going to be a bumpy ride.
Wow, wow, wow, wow!
There's chairs over here, and they're free seating.
And you can just look out.
Or you can go outside in a little bit.
Oh, wow.
Let's go outside.
A little bit of sea breeze.
Let's take a walk.
Gentlemen.
Yes, sir?
Wow, that's a sound.
Wow!
It's so powerful!
Feels so good!
It's cool!
Yoo-hoo!
Wow!Amazing!!!
The water pressure is amazing!
It's like a little splash!
It's amazing!
It's about 65 to 70 kilometers.
It takes about 3 hours and 40 minutes.
So it's about 200 kilometers? What's the distance?
About 200 kilometers, 210 kilometers.
So it takes about 3 hours to get there, and then we go over there and do some preparations.
It takes about 40 minutes to get there.
Now, now.
Now!
Ladies and gentlemen, over here is the wheelhouse.
This is the wheelhouse. It's just up ahead.
Go up the stairs to the third floor.
I'd like to show you... that when the ship is in operation.
I wish I could show you, but as you can see, it's a restricted area.
I hope to be able to show you the rest of the ship next time.
This is the center of the ship, where the captain and the town manager are controlling the ship.
I don't know the speed or direction with this stick.
And before that, on this side, you can see a nautical chart or a kind of magenta map of the ship.
There's a lot of machinery here.
This is the standard class on the first floor.
Seat 382 for the general public.
Oh, it's full!
I often see this kind of scenery in TV dramas.
You can buy a set meal at the store at home
and eat and drink in this eating and drinking space.
It's nice.
Wow!
Cute!
This is the kids' room.
There's a slide for the kids to play inside.
Wow!
One of the kids was just here.
Good morning!
Wow!
That's great.
The snow is so beautiful.
It's nice.
I want to play
We even have a children's washing slide.
There are 120 seats in total, and we have prepared seating that is a little different from the first floor.
Wow, so you have about 500 people spread out all over the ship at once?
Yes, that's right. The entire ship can accommodate 502 people.
That's amazing.
The best part of the double seating is the observation seats in the front, and there are unreserved seats, so let's take a look at the front.
Wow, wow, wow.
It's moving closer.
It's true. It's the opposite of what we saw before.
It's the opposite of what we saw before.
When we get a little closer to the mountain, it will be a little clearer,
Maybe we will be able to see that beautiful view of Mt.
How was your visit to Queen Beer?
Cute. Cute. Cute.
It's very stylish.
It's stylish.
It's really something.
The sea from the second floor is totally different from the sea from the first floor, and when I went outside, it was totally different, so I really enjoyed it.
It felt good to be outside. It felt good. Which view did you like best?
Outside?
It was very powerful. Yes, it was. The water splashing around. It felt great.
Now that you are on your way to Pusan, what do you want to do with the students over there?
I would like to be able to skate a little bit. I want to get to know them well enough to have a normal conversation with them.
Is there any Korean language you are learning now?
When you came to the Tokai before that, you spoke Injeong, right?
Oh, that's right.
But if someone says something to you, just write down "Injeong.
Sorry.
Do you have any ambitions, or any hopes for this kind of exchange?
Anyway, I would like to make the exchange more precious and better than the time we spent in Japan.
I want to enjoy the exchange and at the same time, I want to enjoy Korea.
I want to enjoy myself!
I have an image that people of this age group have courage to listen to K-pop music.
I have an image that people of this age group have courage.
I like dance more than K-pop.
I would like to see such performances if there are any.
I'd like to be able to feel that kind of thing.
I have a friend who I became friends with during a previous exchange in Japan.
I'd like to meet with him
I'm looking forward to meeting with him and having some fun.
I'm looking forward to it.
I like K-pop music.
I want to go to various places
I want to go around to stores and stuff.
Wow! You're the first one!
Yay! That's great!
That feels good!
Wow!Amazing!!!
I don't know, but it's great!
Green!
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
Thank you very much!
I thought we could play again.
Let's play again!
Oh, my gosh!
That was cold!
Let's go this way!
That's great!
Congratulations!
Is this your very first time here?
First time!
Really first time!
It's warm!
Thank you!
I don't know what's going on.
I don't know what it is.
I don't know what it is. I don't know what it is. It's a high-end video.
Did you get the foot?
Did you get my foot?
It's you.
Wow.
I kind of regret that.
It's so far over here.
Yeah, it is.
It's perfect.
Awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, super awesome.
Awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome, awesome. Hello.
Thank you very much.
Ran.
This is Clot.
Cuz here it comes.
Oh, my God.
There he is.
LOL!
Arrived on the way back.
There's another one.
I'm going.
They come down in pieces.
They're coming down in pieces.
Here we are.
Hello, everyone.
Thank you very much.
Hello.
Please.
Come here.
I know it's a short time.
I hope you have a good time.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to show you around Korea.
I'll take you to the meeting place.
Thirty-three years old.
That's great.
Please.
The entrance is big
Awesome and beautiful
usted pues to travel downstairs ied a big book
Gu nhưng
I don't understand this time
Amazing!
That's amazing.
Airplane?
Can I come in?
Oh, my God.
Heh heh heh.
Heh.
That's great.
It's so easy.
What's this?
Oh, it's open!
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Wait a minute.
Welcome aboard today.
Wow.
Thank you for flying with us today.
Wow.Wow.
Wow.
Do it.
So there's an air service school.
I know it's new.
That's what we're going to do.
It's an educational facility.
It's big.
I don't want to fly
It's absolutely delicious
It's absolutely delicious.
It's so good!
It's a cafeteria.
You can study here, order in here, whatever you want.
Heh.
There's also a study area in the back.
Wow, they have a lot of stuff here!
The waitresses are cute.
The waitresses are cute?
Prettier than the orchestra?
I love it. It's fun.
I'm Japanese.
Japanese?
Yes, I am.
That's great.
You go to school.
You go to school?
Yes, sir.
What do you study here?
Korean.
Do you have any recommendations for Korean?
Korean language recommendations?
It sounds like a way of life.
Living? What about traveling?
So, if there's a cool guy...
What? He's cool.
I'm cool.
So, if you see anyone cool...
I'm like, "Oh, he's cool.
Explanation of Cake
Like a hair hand
He has a voluminous head.
Cute hair hand voice
Zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz
What would you like to tell aku-chan?
Thank you for watching!
I don't have Japanese manga, but I can write books and regular novels.
I used to read Japanese manga and I read Japanese books.
I like non-fiction,
I read Japanese manga.
Becoming a Mother
Becoming a mother?
She recommends it.
I hear you hold back on time.
Michibata Mikimoto
So beautiful!
It's amazing!
That's amazing.
I love it.
I can't wait.
Wow!
It's so high up.
Beautiful view.
It's scary.
Can I go?
Sure.
Now.
Come with me.
That view over there.
I wonder if this is the fountain.
I heard it's just a coincidence.
Oh, my God!
It's so high!
Is it that high?
Do you want to pretend to fall down?
Oh, my God!
I can see it.
There it is.
Where can you see it?
I see black.
Down, down, down.
Don't you have to go back?
We got here early, too.
The six of us were sleeping like crazy.
Thank you for watching today.
We're getting calls from all over the place.
That's right.
Let's get some shots.Let's take a shot.
Yes, sir.
Before the Asobi competition
Japanese people have a traditional kendama
With kendama
like this
The Kendama
I'll do it all.
And you know what?
Over there.
Airplane.
I'll do it on the plane.
Yeah, like this.
Oh, here comes the kendama.
From here.
Ah!
Here we go. Ready.
A-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh no!
A-ha-ha-ha-ha
A-ha-ha-ha
Okay.
Ssshhhh.
It's hard.
Try it
How do you hold it?
I think it should be like this.
Hold it.
If you succeed, let's go this way.
Okay.
That's too close.
It's so close.
It's going to come out, isn't it?
Se-no
Nice try
I was on it for a moment, wasn't I?
Come on!
Go for it!
I got hit in the finger with one of these before.
It hurt so much that it traumatized him.
I was hoping you'd enjoy playing with it.
I see.
I'll do my best.
Good luck.
Nice try.
Hang in there.
Really close
I think I can do it.
You were on it for a second there, but...
But you're tired.
You're sweating.
Let's get some juice.
It's hot.
Come on.
It's good.
Okay, let's try one.
Second spiced beer.
I'm good at getting it on here
Nice try.
Fast forward.
If you hit it, I think you can stop this move.
Fast forward
I'm scared.
Now I'm going to show you that by this November, we're going to make it.
I'm looking forward to it. Yes!
I'm practicing every day. Good luck.
It's so fluffy!
It's so hard.
It's hard.
At the bottom.
Around here.
I'll try my best to dye it yellow by November.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Concert in 1 day
1,2,3
One, two, three.
Heart
This is a request
One, two, three.
One, two, three.1,2,3
We've been through a day of exchanges.
How was your day?
Today was fun.
We played games.
Nanami was great.
She was great.
And Kendama was great.
He's working so hard.
How was it?
I'll see you all on November 2nd.
Dancing and Singing.
For the second time.
We're all in.
How was it?
I'm really looking forward to it.
We'll see you tomorrow.
That's right, you three are coming tomorrow.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Tomorrow.
Toyama has three or four oceans.
There are three or four.
Among them...
I'm going to enjoy the most famous one.
I'm sure that's what they're planning to do.
I guess that's the plan.
Well, then, let's all enjoy it together.
Have fun.
I look forward to seeing you tomorrow.
I look forward to working with you.
I see that you have been given four drinks each as
So, I'm very hungry.
with real music on my front face.
I will talk to you.
Well, thank you for watching until the end.
I only bought one of each of you.
Oh!
I'm getting into the spirit of things!
Seino!
Thank you so much for your hard work.
You're so beautiful!